SHAIKH MAJID ALI SHOKAT ALI[1.T.I.]

ADDRESS: 25,PANNALAL CHAWL, SARASPUR AHMEDABAD -380018

Mobile : +917990561656

E-Mail ID: shaikhmajidali73@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE...

To begin as an executive position in the Marketing and gain experience in the functions in the field and also utilize my organizational and customer. Ability to grab career advancement through large effort and innovative work techniques.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS...

DEGREE	UNIVERSITY	YEAR	PERCENTAGE	CLASS
S.S.C	G.S.E.B	2008	64.38%	2 nd
I.T.I. Electrician	N.C.V.T.	2011	71 %	1 st

COMPENTENCY SKILLS...

- Team player with an ability to grasp new thingsquickly.
- Strong analytical, problem solving, organizationalability.
- Ability to deal with peoplediplomatically.
- Willingness tolearn.

COMPUTING SKILLS...

- Microsoft officetools.
- Internet use for Personaluse.

WORK EXPERIENCE...

- At present working with KATARIA TRUCKING PVT LTD(BHARATBENZ),AHMEDABAD As A Electrician since 1^{st Dec} ,2019 to present. Also having a Skill of A.C.
- Working with **YELLOW LINE ENG. PVT LTD**. Ahmedabad As a Electrician from 2012 to 2015 .
- Working with **KATARIA AUTOMOBILE** (Maruti suzuki).Dariyapur Ahmedabad As a Electrician from 2015 to 2018.
- Working with **KATARIA AUTOMOBILE**(BHARATBENZ)Chacharwadi, Ahmedabad As a Electrician from 2018 to Still.

PERSONAL PROFILE...

DateofBirth : 01 / 06 / 1992

Religion :Muslim

Gender : Male

MaritalStatus :Single

Nationality :Indian

LanguagesKnown: Gujarati, Hindi, English, Urdu, Arbi, Persion

Hobbies : Reading

Place: - AHMEDABAD

(MAJID S. SHAIKH)